Lu la lu la.
Piano wa sekai no yume saku nohara ni merodii
A piano sends its melody to the fields of dreams all over the world.
kowareta tokei o shinjite
Believing the broken clock,
jikan wa dare no mikata?
Whose side is time on?
doushite konna ni watashi no mune yasashii dareka o matteru no?
Why is my heart waiting so eagerly for someone kind?
oshiete suteki na mirai
Tell me my wonderful future.
Moonlight, moonlight sleepin'.
Lu la lu la.
omoide ringo ni mezame no shoujo ga kisu shite
A girl awakens to the apple of memories and bestows a kiss.
setsunaku hirogeta hon ni wa
In the book spread open in sorrow,
futari no beru ga naru yo
Their bell rings.
dakishimetai kara itoshii hito
Because I want to hug the one dear to me,
mou nakanaide ne Goodbye Sadness
Don't cry anymore, goodbye sadness.
fushigi na tobira no moji wa "soramimi keiki"
The letters on the mysterious door say "fancy hearing cake".
Wonderland!
youkoso kimi ni wa
Welcome, for you...
Fairyland!
ai no mahou mano
It's the magic of love.
Love's all way!
mainichi fuwa-fuwa komugi no yuuwaku
Everyday, the fluffy temptation of wheat.
Cake for you!
tabete ne konya wa
Please eat, tonight...
Tea for you!
seiza no ochakai
Is a tea party of constellations.
mado ni tenshi no kourasu
A chorus of angels at the window.
kimi ni wa soramimi?
Did you just fancy hearing that?
sukidayo sukidayo no koe
The voices saying "I love you. I love you."
Good morning!
Separation
I can't get it off...
Miss Osaka, good morning.
Chiyo-chan, thank you.
We'll finally be third year students starting today.
Let's do our best!
Yeah, let's do our best.
Not good. Havin' to go all the way to the third floor everyday...
I think I'm gonna lose heart.
That was quick.
Good morning!
Mornin'.
Morning.
I guess we're all together again.
Where are Tomo-chan and Kaorin?
Tomo's not here yet. Kaorin ended up in a different class.
I see. That's really too bad.
Hi, there, everyone! Morning!
Oh!
You cut your hair?
Yeah, chopped it all off yesterday.
What do you think?
Are even the spring fairies taken aback by my new charm?
After all, I've become a third year student now.
I feel like she just reverted back to a first year student...
But why did you cu...
No way, no way!
I didn't think so.
Why did you cut it all off?
Something about this bothers me, but oh well.
Last year, I was growing my hair out, going for a sexy look.
Basically, I was aiming for the Fujiko-chan look.
Huh?
Fujiko-chan?
Aim for her look? But you're not anything like her to begin with.
No, I was actually getting pretty close except for my bust size.
How so?
Lupin!
That's why I gave up trying to go the Fujiko-chan route!
And?
But I could at least shoot for Ayu, you know?
At least?
Chiyo-chan, it's okay to get angry at times like this!
I am Yukari Tanizaki, the homeroom teacher of Class 3.
This year, you all are students studying for entrance exams.
I'm sure you'll be stressed out a lot and it'll be rough for you.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
But it's even rougher for people already in the work force.
So, you better not come looking for pity.
Don't act like tragic victims of the modern education system!
Doesn't Yukari-chan seem a little riled up?
Who knows?
I mean, if you don't want to study, then don't go to college.
Then did you go to college because you wanted to study?
Hah! Like hell I did.
I wonder if she's got some psychological scar
that she can't talk about?
But she's always like this...
Listen here. You guys only have to worry about your own entrance exams,
but I have to think about the exams of several dozen people!
I wonder if Yukari-chan might not be suited to be a teacher.
If you say that, there's no hope for her.
Maybe I'll just not think about them...
I feel like I'm forgetting something important, but...
I am Kimura, the homeroom teacher of Class 4.
Yukari's Birthday
Congratulations!
Happy birthday!
What? Really?! Thank you!
Miss Kurosawa, please open it.
Okay.
Kurosawa!
What did you get?!
A handbag...
Wow...
Well, I've got handbags too!
I'm sure.
You know, you're better off not having handbags anyway!
Why is that?
She is a bad person!
What?!
I'm an adult, you know! There's nothing fun about birthdays!
We can hear every word...
Come to think of it, this year, again...
We didn't give her anything.
Nyamo-chan got somethin' last year too.
What is it, Nyamo? You're all smiles.
Here, look.
The kids in the class gave them to me for my birthday present.
I sort of wonder if I make them feel like they need to do this,
but it still makes me happy, you know?
What's wrong?
What the hell is with you?!
You think you've become the teacher in one of those youth dramas?!
What are you so mad about?
Yukari-chan's actin' kinda weird today.
Yeah, she's oddly quiet...
Oh, that's right.
Miss Kurosawa, who teaches the class next door,
apparently got a present for her birthday from the kids in her class.
When is your birthday, Miss Yukari?
It's passed already.
We can't help it. Yukari-chan's birthday is during spring vacation.
I feel bad. Let's get her something now, even if it's late.
Who the hell needs presents anyway?!
We're sorry.
Happy birthday, huh?
Morning.
Um, Miss Yukari.
We know it's late,
but this is a birthday present from all of us in the class.
What?
This is...
Are you telling me to give it to Nyamo?!
No! This is for you!
A present... for me?
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Yukari-chan!
Happy birthday to you!
Is she happy?
Oh, it's a handbag.
I'm going out for a bit!
She's gone to show it off to Class 2.
Though, it's really great that she's happy 'bout it.
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Kimurin!
Kimurin?
Happy birthday to me.
"Me"?
"This and That On
Career Paths"
Flap Your Wings, Chiyo
Ooh, what's that? Career paths?
Yes. We are third year students, after all.
That's right, we're students studying for entrance exams now.
Entrance exams?
What?
Ah-ha, I get it! You're going for a sports scholarship, aren't you?!
Shut up! What are you going to do?!
What? Me? ICPO.
What's ICPO?
Interpol!
Whoa!
International police!
Whoa, that's amazing! What are you, a kid?!
But does that really exist?
I always thought it was just in the movies.
What?! It doesn't exist?!
ICPO exists.
See? It exists!
How do you join them?
No idea!
I wonder how you do it?
Do you become a police officer first and then get chosen from there?
What?! Is that how it works?!
I don't really know.
Or rather, you sure don't know anything about this
for wanting to become a part of it.
I see, so Tomo-chan's gonna be a police officer.
No, I said, ICPO.
Oh, yeah! Speakin' of police,
there's somethin' I've been wonderin' about.
Listen when someone's talking to you.
That's right! What's written in the police pocketbook?!
Does it have an address notebook or memo notebook
attached to the back after all?
Now that you mention it...
It's got the suspect's phone number and address and such written in it!
Wow, so convenient!
Yeah, right.
Oh...
Then maybe it's got the photo of the person they like in there?
The photo of the policewoman they like or print club stickers.
A policewoman, huh?!
But it'll be rough if a policeman falls for ya.
You know, they tail people and stuff.
That wouldn't be good.
What happened to talking about ICPO?
Chiyo-chan, are you going to apply to a university?
Like Tokyo University?
Oh, no. I'm thinking of going overseas.
What? Studying abroad?!
Yes, especially since American schools
are used to accepting children who have skipped grades.
Awesome! Studying overseas, huh?
There was Sasaki and Ichiro, and now you're next, huh?
That's a little different.
Chiyo-chan says she's going to study abroad. Isn't that amazing?
Yeah, it's amazing.
No, it's nothing so...
She'll get killed.
Yeah.
'Cause your family's rich and you're tiny.
And you're easy to catch.
When you put it that way...
But if it ever comes to that, Mr. Tadakichi will protect me!
Bang!
Mr. Tadakichi has been shot.
What?!
Then what should I do?
Oh, put your genius to good use, like in the dramas,
resist futilely,
and get killed.
Don't worry.
If it ever comes to that, your father will...
My father?
Help!
Stop right there!
I'm sure he'll come flying.
You think so?
Bang!
What?! My father too?!
Don't worry, he deflected it!
No way!
Child President
Child President But studying abroad in America? Did your parents say okay?
Yes. They said to go and see more of the world.
Let your darlin' children travel.
Chiyo-chan, you're darlin'.
Travelin' is okay!
All right, since you're doing this, let's make you president!
That wouldn't be possible.
We'll make America Chiyo-chan's country!
When you do, give me Hawaii and stuff, okay?
Like I said, it's not possible.
Chiyo-chan's country, huh?
I'd wanna go visit.
I bet she's thinking about something weird again.
It's America!
Hello!
Hello! Hello! Hello! Hello!
Welcome to our country!
Welcome!
The little Chiyo-chans are so cute.
We will carry your luggage!
We will!
You sure? Thanks a bunch.
Let us go!
Let's! Let's!
That'd be nice...
Was it okay for us to leave Miss Osaka behind?
She probably won't be coming back for a while.
Yeah.
Pork Buns
Their pork buns are supposed to be good!
Really?
You know a lot about these things, you know that?
Don't they have pizza buns or gratin buns?
This place only sells pork buns!
Okay! I guess I'll buy a snack on the way home for once!
Hey, that was fast!
Wow...
What?
Oh, nothing.
They don't use sugar or anything in pork buns, so it's okay.
Well, well, how convenient for you.
Oh, it's yummy!
It really is delicious!
This has gotta be 100% beef!
That's pork!
That was delicious.
Pork buns really are the standard to go by.
No, I'd have a hard time giving up octopus ball buns too.
I've never had that. Do they really have those?
These days, they have everything.
What's your favorite food? Shark fins?
They have shark fin buns too.
Let me think...
Meatballs!
Whoa, there's a kid here!
I am not a kid!
You're a kid, you're a kid! You're a kid!
Then, what do you like?!
Bananas, I guess.
Whoa, there's an idiot here!
Why do you say that?!
Chiyo-chan!
Miruchi! Yuka!
Who are they?
They're my classmates from back in grade school.
Hello.
What? You're a middle school student already?
What are you saying? I'm a high school student.
Look, we've got sailor uniforms now too.
Wow! I never got to wear those. You're so lucky.
But I'll never get to wear the uniform you're wearing either,
because your school is hard.
You must all be very good at school.
Yeah.
What?!
Our school allows for quite a bit of freedom,
so we get a lot of people who skip classes and fail out too.
Really?
Not me, though.
Some get into Tokyo University, while some can't get in anywhere.
Bye-bye! See you later!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for waiting.
It's not me, right?
It is you!
Please Be Strong
Now, for this part...
Kaorin.
Please don't call me Kaorin.
But everyone calls you that!
But why am I the only one being called by a nickname?!
Then, you can also call me Kimurin.
Like I'm saying...
What? You've become the class representative?
More like made to be than became...
What? Bullying?
I think it's the opposite of bullying.
Representative Assistant Representative
Well, since we don't seem to have any candidates,
I'd like to decide this through nominations.
Does anyone have someone they'd like to nominate for representative?
Me! I think Kaorin would do a great job!
Any others?
Kimura likes me!
Worse than bullying?!
So, I'm stuck with Kimura for the next year...
Miss Sakaki is still so cool!
Why? Why am I the only one in a different class?!
I got to see you again today.
I'm so happy.
Why? Why am I the only one in a different class?!
Excuse me...
Excuse me, how do I get to the faculty office?
It's Kimura's wife.
I'm so sorry. My husband forgot his lunch at home.
I guess he's rather absentminded.
The "love wife lunch"!
I've come here before, but I just can't remember.
To get to the faculty office, go in there, go up the stairs,
and it's at the back of the second floor.
Thank you.
She's such a good person.
That's right. If he has a good person like her for a wife,
Mr. Kimura must have his good points too.
This whole year, I've got Mr. Kimura for my homeroom teacher,
so I'll look for his good points!
Tending a flower garden?
I didn't know he had a side to him like that.
Hi, Kaorin.
Mr. Kimura, are you tending some flowers? What kind of flower...
Kimurin and Kaorin's Flower Garden
Good points are just...
Like hell I can find any!
kokoro ni hane wo motte
With wings upon your soul,
tsutaete mune no sasayaki
Convey the whispers of your heart.
ima, kaze ni notte
Now, riding the wind,
kokoro wa hoshi no kanata (hoshi no kanata)
Your soul is beyond the stars (beyond the stars).
negai wa kanarazu kanau
Your wishes will come true, without fail.
ai ni kite sono kagi wa mirai he
Come see me, that key is for the future.
mado ni sotto yobu koe wa
The voice calling softly by the window
koi no yokan soshite
Speaks of love to come and...
mada touku no ai de mo
Even if the love is still far off,
shinjiteru asu wo shinjiteru kimi wo
I have faith in tomorrow, I have faith in you.
Raspberry heaven.
hitori ja naitte yakusoku shita ne heaven
I promised you that you're not alone, remember, heaven?
Raspberry Heaven amai namida
Raspberry heaven... such sweet tears.
rakuen de mata hohoende ne
Smile again in paradise.
Raspberry heaven.
mukae ni kita yasashii yume no heaven
I've come for you, the heaven of gentle dreams.
Raspberry heaven, I'm coming back to you.
rakuen no hana saita hi ni
On the day the flowers in paradise bloom,
kimi to futari...
You and I...
futari de aimashou
Let's meet, just the two of us.
Next
Azumanga
Daioh
Next week is the school trip in Okinawa!
Shiisaa.
This will be my first time, so I can't wait!
Saataa andagii.
I've got super big expectations for diving, too!
Bitter melon champloo.
I might get to see an iriomote cat.
Yamapikaryaa!
Everyone, together now...
Haisai!