Lu la lu la.
Piano wa sekai no yume saku nohara ni merodii
A piano sends its melody to the fields of dreams all over the world.
kowareta tokei o shinjite
Believing the broken clock,
jikan wa dare no mikata?
Whose side is time on?
doushite konna ni watashi no mune yasashii dareka o matteru no?
Why is my heart waiting so eagerly for someone kind?
oshiete suteki na mirai
Tell me my wonderful future.
Moonlight, moonlight sleepin'.
Lu la lu la.
omoide ringo ni mezame no shoujo ga kisu shite
A girl awakens to the apple of memories and bestows a kiss.
setsunaku hirogeta hon ni wa
In the book spread open in sorrow,
futari no beru ga naru yo
Their bell rings.
dakishimetai kara itoshii hito
Because I want to hug the one dear to me,
mou nakanaide ne Goodbye Sadness
Don't cry anymore, goodbye sadness.
fushigi na tobira no moji wa "soramimi keiki"
The letters on the mysterious door say "fancy hearing cake".
Wonderland!
youkoso kimi ni wa
Welcome, for you...
Fairyland!
ai no mahou mano
It's the magic of love.
Love's all way!
mainichi fuwa-fuwa komugi no yuuwaku
Everyday, the fluffy temptation of wheat.
Cake for you!
tabete ne konya wa
Please eat, tonight...
Tea for you!
seiza no ochakai
Is a tea party of constellations.
mado ni tenshi no kourasu
A chorus of angels at the window.
kimi ni wa soramimi?
Did you just fancy hearing that?
sukidayo sukidayo no koe
The voices saying "I love you. I love you."
Yomi's Exposure to the World
I had no idea.
Yeah. That's why I told 'em...
Hello, my friends. Happy New Year.
Oh, Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
How was everyone's New Year's?
I spent it utterly relaxed at the warm heated table.
I was meltin'...
It was a quiet New Year's.
What about you, Miss Yomi?
Wait!
Wait, wait!
How was your New Year's, Miss Yomi?
You mustn't ask!
I went for a quick trip to Hokkaido.
Wow!
By the way, have you all been on an airplane before?
Oh, no.
Me, neither.
No!
I have!
Chiyo-chan, why don't we go over here for a little chat?
It was your first time too!
Here, souvenirs.
Yay!
Thank you.
[ Box: White Friend ]
"White Friend, Black"?
Sakaki.
Here.
Hokkaido Specialty
Bear Stew
Lots of Vegetables
I'd heard that you like bears and things, so...
It's got bear in it.
Wow, lucky you. Isn't this great, Miss Sakaki?
Oh!
Yomi!
During...
New Year's...
you gained...
a little weight, didn't you?!
Bull's-eye, is it?!
Did you loosen up in Hokkaido and eat too much?! Is that it?!
Say it! Was it rice cakes?! Or sweet red bean soup?!
-abs...
Eh? Say that again? Eh?!
Crabs...
It was all you can eat, so...
All you can eat?! Crabs?! You idiot!
I'm going to go tell Miss Yukari!
In Hokkaido?!
Crabs?!
All you can eat?!
Yomi did it, Yomi did it...
You really brought her!
Was it good? Was it good?! It was good, wasn't it?!
Yes...
You had more than just crabs, right?! What else did you eat?!
Like Genghis Khan...
Genghis Khan
Genghis Khan?!
What was Genghis Khan again?
I don't know, ma'am.
We'll ask Chiyo-chan.
Just you remember this!
Genghis Khan is a Hokkaido specialty,
where mutton is cooked in a slightly different kind of pan.
Oh...
Is that good?
It's delicious.
What else?! You had other kinds of fun too, didn't you?!
Oh! You went to a hot spring, didn't you?!
An open-air bath...
Oh, my!
Outdoors?! In the nude?!
Pervert!
What are you saying?!
So, which hot spring?
Noboribetsu.
Noboribetsu?
Noboribetsu Karls!
Oh, I know! It's that white bath salt!
I've bathed in that before!
Noboribetsu's great, isn't it?! After all, it is Noboribetsu!
Whoa! She thinks they've got something in common just because she used the bath salt!
It's exceptional, you know?!
I hear the bears in the area all bathe there too!
I'll quit bragging from now on.
Hurray for hot springs! Hurray!
Especially to these guys.
Viva hot springs!
Betrayal
Which one should I get?
This one!
Oh, the cup!
My milk tea!
Stop! Stop!
What a calamity.
I trusted you...
Would you like some?
I can never use this vending machine again out of fear.
Trust in you has just plummeted, my friend.
What are you doing?
Ya see...
Oh, my dear Koyomi, buy some juice.
I don't need you to tell me that. It's what I came here for.
I think I'll get milk tea.
Huh? It came with two cups.
What?
It can't be!
What is it?
Did I do something?
Lunch Break...
So, I got to ski too.
It was all powdery snow and not packed together at all.
Was it really?
Wow, udon with curry, huh? I didn't think of that.
Udon with curry!
It's dangerous! Everyone run! This stuff splatters!
Don't worry, I'll be careful.
Being careful is useless! It splatters no matter what!
And in the end, you'll be covered in curry!
Finally, it's Yomi's time to have a miserable food experience too!
Wow, you're good.
You haven't splattered at all. You're somethin' else.
You're amazing, Miss Yomi.
I've loved udon ever since I was small, so that's why.
Damn you, it's unforgivable!
You've been so weird, what's gotten into you?!
What's with you today?!
Don't run!
Tomo-chan!
Whoa, whoa, stay away from me!
Stop right there!
The town's in an uproar!
Ow...
Wait! We can talk about this.
My grudge over the milk tea...
No, that's not all.
My grudge over the crabs and my grudge over the Genghis Khan too!
I won't let you have all the fun!
Why me?!
It's all soggy now.
Excited, Excited, Excited, Excited
If you don't hurry, I'm leaving.
Wait for me!
Miss Osaka, let's go home.
What are you reading?
Information pamphlets.
Hearin' about Yomi-chan's stories of Hokkaido
made me feel like I wanted to go somewhere too.
[ Page: Magical Land ]
And I found someplace that looks interestin'.
Oh, that's Magical Land, isn't it?!
Magical Land?
It's a theme park that opened just the other day.
I've been wanting to go there.
Really?
I know! Why don't we all go there this upcoming weekend?
Sounds nice.
I agree!
If it's plans like that, let me in!
I'm in! I'll get in! How could I not?! Yay! Yay!
You certainly are energetic.
An amusement park! An amusement park! Woohoo!
Such a child.
What did you say?!
Then are you saying you aren't looking forward to it?!
Well, at the very least, not so much that I'd get as excited as you.
Hah! Acting all mature!
And thus, your eyes had lost the glimmer of childhood!
What's that supposed to mean?
Yomi-chan, Yomi-chan, there's big news!
The rollercoaster there's the best in Japan.
Absolute Terror
Anaconda
Japan's Greatest Terror Has Arrived
Wow.
That has a nice ring to it, "the best in Japan"!
It's apparently somehow really terrifying.
They seem to have a lot of people who start cryin' too.
And this attraction next to it looks incredibly fun as well.
Wow...
See? Yomi's beginning to get excited too.
Oh, I can see it. I can see it!
Yomi running around like a little kid.
Oh, there, there. She tripped. Don't cry, don't cry.
Quit seeing weird things!
Several Days Later...
Book Store
Oh, Miss Yomi!
Oh! Oh, Chiyo-chan!
Oh, are you out shopping?
What? Well, something like that.
I came to buy the guidebook to Magical Land.
After all, it's finally tomorrow. I'm so excited!
Are you?
What did you buy, Miss Yomi?
What? Oh, a reference book.
Oh, my mom asked me to do some shopping for her.
I'll see you later, Chiyo-chan!
Oh, okay.
See you tomorrow!
Okay!
Magical Land
Oh, no...
Not good. Did I catch a chill?
This might not be possible...
This too...
Oh, we have to do this one.
Oh! I'm definitely getting on this ride!
I'll get on it even if I have to wait 50 minutes.
What? You sometimes have to wait an hour?
What to do?
No, but...
Will Tomo be able to wait that long?
Oh, these are linked! Then we gotta...
There we go!
There, there.
Yup?
Oh, it's you.
What? You can't go?! Why?
A fever?!
What?! Miss Yomi has a fever?!
She said she suddenly got it this morning.
Left Out
What the heck? That sure sucks for Yomi.
Then, let's cancel today's trip and go visit Miss Yomi.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Chiyo-chan.
Yes?
Chiyo-chan, you're such a child when it comes to these things.
Listen to me. If we did that, Yomi would be concerned for us, see?
So, the correct thing to do here is to leave Yomi alone
and go have all the fun we can!
What? Uh, is it really?
So, now that we've settled that, off we go!
Yay!
Running on stairs is dangerous!
Being rowdy on the train platform is dangerous!
Let's go!
By now, everyone's...
Oh, but maybe they'll try to surprise me and come visit.
Koyomi, you have a phone call from Miss Takino.
Yes?
Hello? Oh, Yomi? We're getting on a rollercoaster now!
So, I'll broadcast it to you live!
Hey!
Koyomi, you have a phone call from Chiyo-chan.
Yes?
Oh, Miss Yomi, are you okay? Has your fever gone down?
Yeah, quite a bit.
Bad girl!
You shouldn't have gotten carried away and fallen asleep naked.
Hold on a second! What the heck is that supposed to mean?!
Was it Tomo?! Did Tomo say that?!
What? Oh...
Get her on the phone for me!
All right, I'll switch right now, so please wait a minute.
Sure.
Whoa!
Um, Tomo-chan...
That was fun!
Well...
Oh, what's that thing?
The phone...
Please wait!
That thing over there!
Miss Yomi is on the phone!
Wow, awesome! Did you see? Did you just see that?!
That'll kill ya. Just kill ya.
Hello?
Let's go on that next! Go! Go!
Hello?!
Good morning!
Morning.
Morning, Yomi.
Good morning.
Miss Yomi, I guess you're better now.
It was really too bad about yesterday.
Oh, thanks. Did you have fun yesterday?
Should I tell her honestly that I had a good time? Or...
Man, it was the best!
Every attraction was just really awesome!
But there were so many people, it sure was rough.
Yeah, the crowd was huge and we got tired just from that.
But no matter how much we had to wait,
every ride we got on sure was worth it.
Really, Miss Kagura, ain't that the truth?
Tomo-chan, where're ya from again?
Come to think of it, Tomo-chan sure was noisy that time.
Oh, that? The guy in front was really obnoxious.
Yeah, yeah, and on top of that...
Um...
This is a souvenir for you.
And that thing came flying.
Sweating like crazy in the winter.
Thank you, Chiyo-chan.
It's no laughing...
matter!
Now, now.
I made a mistake!
If we didn't enjoy life as much as we do,
you couldn't have fun with it, even if you wanted to.
You're exactly right.
So, you know? It was a really good thing that you couldn't come.
What?
Yomi's snapped!
Go!
Um, Miss Yomi.
Earlier, well...
There's nothing you need to apologize for, Chiyo-chan.
So...
This is the real souvenir.
Thank you.
Wow.
The thing inside is the mascot of Magical Land.
Thank you, Chiyo-chan.
Miss Yomi.
Let's all go together next time.
Yeah.
No wonder it's cold.
Snow?
Wow, you're right!
Pretty, isn't it?
I hope it'll pile up.
Yeah.
So white!
Awesome...
It's so pretty!
Let's do something! Let's do something! Let's do something!
Snowball fight!
Yeah!
That's it!
Yay!
It doesn't hurt, even if ya fall.
You'll pay if you let your guard down!
Exactly!
Now you've done it!
There, there!
It's so cold!
I can't hit anyone at all.
Miss Sakaki, you're amazing!
No, well...
It's a mess.
Here goes!
Don't underestimate someone who's been to Hokkaido!
Oh, yeah?!
Here goes!
Wow, that was cool!
Tomo-chan, that's not fair!
What?
Stupid...
kokoro ni hane wo motte
With wings upon your soul,
tsutaete mune no sasayaki
Convey the whispers of your heart.
ima, kaze ni notte
Now, riding the wind,
kokoro wa hoshi no kanata (hoshi no kanata)
Your soul is beyond the stars (beyond the stars).
negai wa kanarazu kanau
Your wishes will come true, without fail.
ai ni kite sono kagi wa mirai he
Come see me, that key is for the future.
mado ni sotto yobu koe wa
The voice calling softly by the window
koi no yokan soshite
Speaks of love to come and...
mada touku no ai de mo
Even if the love is still far off,
shinjiteru asu wo shinjiteru kimi wo
I have faith in tomorrow, I have faith in you.
Raspberry heaven.
hitori ja naitte yakusoku shita ne heaven
I promised you that you're not alone, remember, heaven?
Raspberry Heaven amai namida
Raspberry heaven... such sweet tears.
rakuen de mata hohoende ne
Smile again in paradise.
Raspberry heaven.
mukae ni kita yasashii yume no heaven
I've come for you, the heaven of gentle dreams.
Raspberry heaven, I'm coming back to you.
rakuen no hana saita hi ni
On the day the flowers in paradise bloom,
kimi to futari...
You and I...
futari de aimashou
Let's meet, just the two of us.
Next
Azumanga
Daioh
Miss Osaka, what will you do when you grow up?
I haven't really given it much thought.
But ya know, what kind of spring is youth supposed to be?
[ Note: Pun. Youth = Blue Spring ]
Are there such things as red springs or yellow springs?
I don't really know.
Green, purple, orange, light-blue springs...
Please watch us again next week!