Lu la lu la.
Piano wa sekai no yume saku nohara ni merodii
A piano sends its melody to the fields of dreams all over the world.
kowareta tokei o shinjite
Believing the broken clock,
jikan wa dare no mikata?
Whose side is time on?
doushite konna ni watashi no mune yasashii dareka o matteru no?
Why is my heart waiting so eagerly for someone kind?
oshiete suteki na mirai
Tell me my wonderful future.
Moonlight, moonlight sleepin'.
Lu la lu la.
omoide ringo ni mezame no shoujo ga kisu shite
A girl awakens to the apple of memories and bestows a kiss.
setsunaku hirogeta hon ni wa
In the book spread open in sorrow,
futari no beru ga naru yo
Their bell rings.
dakishimetai kara itoshii hito
Because I want to hug the one dear to me,
mou nakanaide ne Goodbye Sadness
Don't cry anymore, goodbye sadness.
fushigi na tobira no moji wa "soramimi keiki"
The letters on the mysterious door say "fancy hearing cake".
Wonderland!
youkoso kimi ni wa
Welcome, for you...
Fairyland!
ai no mahou mano
It's the magic of love.
Love's all way!
mainichi fuwa-fuwa komugi no yuuwaku
Everyday, the fluffy temptation of wheat.
Cake for you!
tabete ne konya wa
Please eat, tonight...
Tea for you!
seiza no ochakai
Is a tea party of constellations.
mado ni tenshi no kourasu
A chorus of angels at the window.
kimi ni wa soramimi?
Did you just fancy hearing that?
sukidayo sukidayo no koe
The voices saying "I love you. I love you."
Now, next month, there's the long awaited school trip.
Anticipation
You look like you're looking forward to it, Chiyo-chan.
The truth is, the school trip has been canceled.
I'm kidding, that was a lie.
Seeing Chiyo-chan looking so happy, I just couldn't help myself.
Yes!
I can understand.
Now, I've got a guidebook for the school trip here.
I'll read a little of it for you.
Let's see, "The school trip is not for having fun."
Changed Hairstyle
"Be fully aware that it is a part of your studies..."
That's what it says, but it's really about having fun, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
But don't underestimate the challenge of having fun!
Having fun in an unfamiliar town
in a limited amount of time is hard, you know.
Several of you are sure to end your school trip with regrets.
Heh Heh Heh Heh Heh Heh Heh Heh Heh.
At last, the school trip!
This will be my first time on a school trip!
Oh, that's right.
You left before you finished grade school, didn't you?
Yes!
Then, I will teach you the rules of going on school trips.
Rules?
For a souvenir, buy a wooden sword!
A wooden sword?!
And a Shinsengumi livery coat to go with the wooden sword!
A livery coat?!
A livery coat...
Chiyo-chan...
We gotta decide on our group.
She said six people to a group, right?
Yeah.
Then, me, Chiyo-chan, Osaka, and...
Yes!
Sakaki and Kagura...
Wasn't there one group that's allowed to only have five people?
Hey, hey, that's harsh, señor.
Chiyo-chan, want to take a look at the guidebook?
Okay!
Wow!
Oh, I can't wait!
I'll bet it'll be tons of fun.
Yes, I'm sure it will be!
At that time, they never even dreamed
that it would turn out to be such a miserable trip.
Or something.
Don't insert weird narration!
So excited, so excited! One month!
Beach Vacation
Yes?
Hello?
Yomi?
Tomo, it's almost time for Okinawa.
All right, is everyone here?!
If you're not here, raise your hand! Just kidding!
Me! I'm not here!
But you're here!
Okay, we're now going to be heading to Okinawa,
but the school trip is from now until we get home!
Talk about thinking ahead!
Airport souvenirs!
They sure are taking it fast...
Whoa, you're already buying?!
But this is making me a little nervous.
Yeah, with this many people on board, we might not be able to fly.
Whoa, it's going to take off!
Plane captain?!
It's got incredible power!
We can fly with this! We can fly!
Shut up.
Can't Stand Still
Okinawa...
Okinawa!
The sky's so blue!
Hurry!
Stay cool.
Haisai!
Oh, that's Okinawan.
"Hello," was it?
Ow!
What?
What do you say in Okinawan in situations like that?
Situations like that?
Yeah.
Ow, ow!
They apparently say, "Agaa!"
Ooh, so this is the Shureimon Gate.
Yeah, probably. I'll bet.
This is it.
Oh, wow! It's a 2,000 yen bill!
Wow.
You're right, it looks exactly like it.
The Shureimon Gate is in the watermark too.
Yes.
Oh, there're shiisaa here!
How'd you say, "Is that a shiisaa?" In Okinawan?
"Are shiisaa yaibiimi?" I think.
Shiisaa yaibiimi?
Uree shiisaa yaibiin.
Six high school students, please!
Okay, here we go!
Okinawa! Okinawa! Okinawa!
Clap, clap!
Wow...
There're shiisaa lined up here too.
Lemme think...
Shiisaa yaibiin.
Shiisaa yaibiimi?
Are shiisaa aibiran!
Okinawa! Okinawa! Okinawa! Okinawa!
Shut up.
It's the hotel!
Yeah!
Dinner time!
Oh! Buffet!
Limiter removed!
I won't be outdone!
I'm going to eat this too!
There!
There, there, there!
Ooh, it's champloo.
Yes. We're in Okinawa, so we must eat this!
Yeah.
Bitter melon champloo.
Wheat-gluten bread champloo.
Fine noodle champloo.
Let me think, let me think, let me think...
Let me think...
Champloo!
Yesterday was Shurijo Castle and today, it's Manzamou.
Watery Grave
It feels like we're really enjoying the basic tourist course.
Yahoo!
It's a cliff! It's a cliff...
How terrifying!
Chiyo-chan!
Up we go!
There, there, there, there! There, there, there, there, there!
Hey, Tomo, cut it out!
Chiyo-chan!
What are you, an idiot?!
How terrifying!
Osaka, it's over.
Okay, your attention please!
Next up is recreational diving!
I'll be doing this with your group.
Yeah!
This is my super first time diving! I'm super stoked!
Right?!
Oh, I've done it before, but...
Come on, let's toss this brat into the sea!
Sea Slugs
The ocean, the ocean, the ocean, the ocean, the ocean!
Wow, that was really fun!
Yeah.
Yeah! It was super fun!
This isn't something you can describe with just the word "super"!
How do you say...
Awesome...
It was awesome fun!
Kokusaidori
What should I get for souvenirs?
Chinsuko
Chinsuko!
Are you going to buy it?
Shut up...
Oh, these little shiisaa are so cute!
Those are nice.
Their faces are all slightly different from each other,
so it really has that handmade feel to them.
This one. No, this one?
I'm going to get this one!
Shiisaa yaibiin.
Miss Osaka! Miss Kagura!
Yo.
Chiyo-chan!
Hey, what's the matter?
Something smells good.
What?
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
Sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff.
What the heck are you doing?
Oh!
Tomo-chan!
Yo!
What's that? Something sweet?!
Saataa andagii.
Something sweet?!
I'm sorry, we didn't buy any for you two...
Saataa andagii.
How much was it?
It was 100 yen.
Saataa andagii.
Where were they selling...
Oh, shut up!
Saataa andagii.
So, like I said!
What's that?
[ Box: Chinsuko of a Southern Land - 15 Piece Set ]
Oh, this is...
Saataa andagii!
No!
Island of Dreams
Miss Sakaki!
Good morning!
Morning.
Where are you going for today's outlying island trip?
We're going to Miyakojima Island!
I'm going to...
Iriomote cat!
What? Oh, you mean Iriomote Island. I hope you enjoy it!
I will.
What?
That t-shirt...
Oh, I bought it at a shop over there.
No, that...
I'm going to go change!
Oh, we can see it! We can see it!
Then, I'll go over it one more time.
Uebara Harbor
Get on
boat here
Urauchigawa
River
Iriomote
Wildlife Center
Mariyudo Waterfall
National Park
Ohara Harbor
We'll walk along from Ohara Harbor, go to the Wildlife Center,
go all the way around to get on an excursion boat at Urauchigawa River,
and see the Mariyudo Waterfall.
After that, we'll buy souvenirs at Uebara and go home.
Anyway, let's be careful not to miss the boat home.
Yes.
Wow, so that's
the island...
Iriomote!
I'm taking the picture!
I'll switch places with you.
Iriomote Cat Crossing
Wildcat...
"There might be wildcats around! Please slow down."
It says there might be some around!
Oh, awesome!
Then, we better slow down too.
Well...
No need for that.
Do you think we'll get to see an iriomote cat?!
No, that's probably impossible.
I shouldn't expect so much.
Not to mention the fact that they're wildcats.
I might not get off so lightly.
Let's hope there are some cute wildcat character goods.
Yes.
Man, so we're not gonna get to see them?
But with Sakaki,
they might come out to bite, if you put your hand out.
Like this?
Sakaki-chan's like a frog bein' stared down by a snake.
It can't be helped. Kagura!
Roar!
Please wait!
What?
That somewhat tiger-like face! The short-ish legs and thick tail!
The mottled pattern on its body! And those rounded ears!
Yamapikaryaa!
Yamapikaryaa?
Yes.
Yamapikaryaa refers to an iriomote cat in the local language!
Cat of the Mountains
Yamapikaryaa?
Yes!
Oh?
Oh, he's taken a liking to Miss Sakaki!
Wow!
Hey, you can pet him!
All right, Sakaki-chan, go for it!
Pick him up! Give him a big hug!
Big hug!
He's so cute! He's still a kitten, isn't he?
Yamamayaa.
Yamamayaa!
Yamamayaa also means wildcat!
Yamapikaryaa!
I guess he'll also look like that when he grows up.
Yeah.
And then, become like that.
Talk about all bony.
Oh, there's a snake swimming!
Where?!
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
I guess this is goodbye.
In the end, we shouldn't take him back with us.
And I can't keep cats at home, either...
Not to mention the fact that you're a special national monument.
You can't come with us!
Miss Sakaki...
The mother?
Airport souvenir...
[ Box: Turmeric Tea ]
Turmeric tea!
Turmeric tea, turmeric tea! Turmeric tea!
Turmeric tea, turmeric tea, turmeric tea, turmeric tea, turmeric tea!
Shut up!
Okinawa certainly was fun!
It sure was.
Miss Sakaki.
Wouldn't it be nice to come back again?
Yeah.
I'll come again.
kokoro ni hane wo motte
With wings upon your soul,
tsutaete mune no sasayaki
Convey the whispers of your heart.
ima, kaze ni notte
Now, riding the wind,
kokoro wa hoshi no kanata (hoshi no kanata)
Your soul is beyond the stars (beyond the stars).
negai wa kanarazu kanau
Your wishes will come true, without fail.
ai ni kite sono kagi wa mirai he
Come see me, that key is for the future.
mado ni sotto yobu koe wa
The voice calling softly by the window
koi no yokan soshite
Speaks of love to come and...
mada touku no ai de mo
Even if the love is still far off,
shinjiteru asu wo shinjiteru kimi wo
I have faith in tomorrow, I have faith in you.
Raspberry heaven.
hitori ja naitte yakusoku shita ne heaven
I promised you that you're not alone, remember, heaven?
Raspberry Heaven amai namida
Raspberry heaven... such sweet tears.
rakuen de mata hohoende ne
Smile again in paradise.
Raspberry heaven.
mukae ni kita yasashii yume no heaven
I've come for you, the heaven of gentle dreams.
Raspberry heaven, I'm coming back to you.
rakuen no hana saita hi ni
On the day the flowers in paradise bloom,
kimi to futari...
You and I...
futari de aimashou
Let's meet, just the two of us.
Next
Azumanga
Daioh
It's coming, it's coming. It's creeping up.
Look, it's almost here already.
Huh? What? Something's comin'?
What do you think?! Entrance exams! College entrance exams!
Where? Where's it comin'?
Let's go to Chiyo-chan's summer home again this year!
This time, it'll be an entrance exam study camp!
We'll swim! We'll have fun! We'll smash watermelons!
Never mind that! Study!