Lu la lu la.
Piano wa sekai no yume saku nohara ni merodii
A piano sends its melody to the fields of dreams all over the world.
kowareta tokei o shinjite
Believing the broken clock,
jikan wa dare no mikata?
Whose side is time on?
doushite konna ni watashi no mune yasashii dareka o matteru no?
Why is my heart waiting so eagerly for someone kind?
oshiete suteki na mirai
Tell me my wonderful future.
Moonlight, moonlight sleepin'.
Lu la lu la.
omoide ringo ni mezame no shoujo ga kisu shite
A girl awakens to the apple of memories and bestows a kiss.
setsunaku hirogeta hon ni wa
In the book spread open in sorrow,
futari no beru ga naru yo
Their bell rings.
dakishimetai kara itoshii hito
Because I want to hug the one dear to me,
mou nakanaide ne Goodbye Sadness
Don't cry anymore, goodbye sadness.
fushigi na tobira no moji wa "soramimi keiki"
The letters on the mysterious door say "fancy hearing cake".
Wonderland!
youkoso kimi ni wa
Welcome, for you...
Fairyland!
ai no mahou mano
It's the magic of love.
Love's all way!
mainichi fuwa-fuwa komugi no yuuwaku
Everyday, the fluffy temptation of wheat.
Cake for you!
tabete ne konya wa
Please eat, tonight...
Tea for you!
seiza no ochakai
Is a tea party of constellations.
mado ni tenshi no kourasu
A chorus of angels at the window.
kimi ni wa soramimi?
Did you just fancy hearing that?
sukidayo sukidayo no koe
The voices saying "I love you. I love you."
Yawn Master
Oh, Mom...
Yes, I saw the photo.
I'm sure it's probably not a bad match,
but it's too soon for me to be looking at arranged marriages.
How old do you think I am?
What are you saying? It's not as if you're going to be young forever.
And it's not often that you get matches as nice as this one.
From Mom
Yeah...
All right, but I'm only going to meet him, okay?
Sure. I'll give them a call too.
Bye.
From Mom
All right!
It's not as if I'll be young forever...
What are you saying?! I'm still young!
Oh, yes, yes! Yes!
Copy it!!
Man, I can't believe how sleepy I was!
Or rather, you were completely asleep!
Well, I guess it can't be helped with this kind of weather.
For real, the weather sure is nice today, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Sittin' out here in the sunlight,
it feels like I'm bundled up in a nice, fluffy blanket.
Well, it was just such a magnificent yawn,
I couldn't take my eyes off it.
Yes, yes.
Très bien!
Amazing!
It was the very picture of a yawn! I've never seen a yawn like that!
Really?
Yeah!
It's like you've come from the land of yawns to spread yawning!
Hey, yawn master!
You don't have to go that far.
Impressive, Osaka!
I guess all people have at least one redeeming trait.
Now, teach me how to yawn like that!
This is the yawn training hall!
Sure.
Hey, now.
That wasn't quite the same somehow.
Yeah, it wasn't.
Please let me join in too!
I'm going on ahead back to the classroom.
Me too.
Vaguely Youth
Shoot! Afternoon classes have started already!
Oh, it's your fault, Tomo-chan!
Wait for me!
You were sleeping on the roof?! Why?!
Let's see. Because the sky was just so blue, or something?
Smack
You three! Ten laps around the schoolyard!
Honestly! I can't believe those girls!
And they have entrance exams next year!
What's wrong? What are you so irritated about?
It's nothing.
Some girls in your class were apparently practicing yawning
during lunch, and fell asleep.
What do you mean, practicing yawning?
I have no idea!
I don't really get it, but I don't see much wrong with it.
Being easygoing is one of the privileges of adolescence.
Privilege, huh?
But don't you think you can still only take adolescence so far?
Never mind that. You want to go flower gazing?
Flower gazing?
After School
Bye-bye.
Oh, wait for me!
Library
And then, what happened was,
it turned out to be hashed beef instead of curry!
What? You can't even tell hashed beef and curry apart?
Oh, sometimes, I can't tell 'em apart even if I eat 'em.
What?!
That's having way too little sense of taste!
And you're in a position to say that?!
Hey, we're heading home, so...
When you leave, make sure to turn the lights out.
Roger that!
I didn't know it was this late already.
It's already getting dark outside.
You're right.
Shall we go home?
Oh.
That's Miss Kagura, isn't it?
Somehow, it sure makes you feel like we're living our youth.
Basic strength?
Yeah.
Is that for the swim team?
Because I want to make it to the national level this year.
I'm kind of gunning for it.
That's amazin'.
I'd always thought the swim team was on break except for the summer.
You dummy!
Don't think we're the same as you people in the Go-home Club!
Go-home Club? What's the Go-home Club?
Oh, it's the students who aren't in any clubs
and go home as soon as classes are over.
In other words, people like us.
So?
Why were you guys at school this late?
Oh, because she said she needed to look for some book.
We were all at the library together.
But it was more like we were just chatting there.
You guys are lucky, you have this freedom about you.
Freedom?
We're barely getting passing grades and you think we have freedom?
You're freaking dumb!
Oh, Tomo-chan...
Was it really not that funny?!
Hey!
Hey, come on!
Adults' Flower Gazing
Whoa, it's a nice looking place.
I can't believe this!
I would've dressed more properly if I'd known it was a place like this.
You said we were going flower gazing, so...
Huh? Didn't I say we were going to a hotel bar?
That's news to me!
Well, it doesn't matter.
Oh, wait! Oh...
Wow, Eiko, a section chief, huh?
I don't really know how companies work,
but isn't that a pretty big deal?
I suppose, but all I've gotten is more work to do.
The actual work I do hasn't changed.
You reprimand your subordinates and get reprimanded by your supervisor.
Well, my work does directly affects the results of operations,
so I guess in that sense, it's work worth doing.
You're amazing! You seem so grownup, Eiko!
What are you saying? You two are grownups too.
Well, that's true, but...
That's right! We also have important jobs
educating the promising youth of tomorrow!
We're totally grownup!
Say, Miss Minamo, you're a P.E. Teacher, right?
Do you have any intention of switching jobs?
What?
A sports gym affiliated with our company
is looking for a chief instructor.
Naturally, you'd be treated as a full-time employee.
The place is high-class, so you'd undoubtedly double your salary.
Switching jobs...
Come on, don't be so shocked.
I'm just saying, if you feel like it.
I'm sorry. You brought it up so suddenly, it caught me off guard.
Will you think about it?
No, I'm not going to switch jobs, because I love my current job.
But...
But?
It never even occurred to me to even think about switching jobs...
No! Stop it, Eiko!
Without Nyamo, I'd have to walk to school!
What's that mean?
Oh, my eraser...
That's right, both Mother and Father are out today.
Mihama
What should I do?
Hey.
Please spare me! No! No! I'm sorry! Please spare me!
Calm down. Calm down!
What are you doing out here alone at this hour?
I ran out of convenience stores, so I was headed to the eraser...
Going to a convenience store to buy an eraser, huh?
Yes.
I've never gone out alone this late at night before.
Be careful. I've heard...
They show up around here.
What?
What show up?
This.
Oh, it's me.
Yeah, I'm out drinking right now.
Hold on a minute.
Let's see, do you two have anyone special right now?
Nope, nope, nope!
There aren't any scandalous stories to tell about us lately.
Okay! We've got the right number of people too! Hurry on over, okay?
What was that about?
Actually, I told the boys at work about you two.
They're both pretty nice guys.
Children's Flower Gazing
Thank you very much.
This is like going flower gazing.
Thanks for treating me.
Not a problem. After all, you walked me to the convenience store.
Couldn't very well leave you alone when you looked at me that way.
Going to the convenience store at night is such fun.
I guess once you're grownup,
you can even shop in the middle of the night.
That must be so nice. I can't wait to grow up.
So, you can't wait to grow up, huh, Chiyo-chan?
And you can, Miss Kagura?
Well, I'd never really thought about it much.
Thinking about me going to work and getting married...
I can't imagine that just yet.
Going to work and getting married...
That's true, it's a little hard to imagine.
Well, in your case, you're still little,
so I don't think that's surprising.
Do you think so?
Yeah.
But I still can't wait to grow up!
Hey, good evening! I'm Nakku, aka Nakuro Tanaka!
I'm Mitchy, aka Michiru Ogino!
This is Nakku...
and Mitchy's...
Thrilling Main Street of Youth!
But you know, Mitchy, did you see the cherry blossoms in town?
They're sure blooming early this year.
Yeah, I saw!
Like the cherry trees in the park near the studio are in full bloom!
I'll bet people who were planning on going flower gazing
next week or the week after are pretty disappointed.
Yo.
So, you came.
If you don't change your plans and go soon, it's all going to be gone.
Yeah.
I know. Cherry blossoms scatter, you know?
I love cherry blossoms, but I don't like watching them scatter.
I'm not going to pay any attention to you!
It's sad watching something beautiful scatter.
I don't mind.
That's why I don't really like flower gazing that much.
Well, I can understand how you feel,
but I think maybe the beauty of flowers strike people's hearts
because they blossom so brilliantly, then scatter just as quickly.
Hey, wasn't that yawn just now good?
You were still doing that?
Honestly! Those men left because you just had to say that!
My mistake, my mistake.
I thought it'd be funny. Guess it was pretty far off the mark.
Your attitude really hasn't changed since our college days.
Oh, who cares if those silly guys don't like us?
Who are you calling silly guys?
I thought you actually liked them quite a bit.
Oh! Is that it, Nyamo?!
Did you want to catch a guy that badly?!
Would it be wrong if I did?!
Oh, is that so? Well, so very, very sorry then!
Damn it! Let's go drink another round!
I'm all for that!
Let's see, the pen name is Rice Cake With Bean Jam Chocolate.
That's an awfully sweet sounding name.
Well, Rice Cake With Bean Jam Chocolate has requested
Yu Asakawa's "My Heart Is That Of A Little Girl and I Parachute"!
Oh, I love this song!
Come to think of it...
What?
You know how today,
Kagura was saying something about us having freedom?
I wonder what that was supposed to mean?
Oh, that.
Well, I think she meant that, be it club activities or studying,
if you're working really hard at it, you sometimes get frantic
about whether you'll be able to accomplish your goals or not.
There's nothing that we're working really hard at. She probably meant
we have more freedom because we have nothing to be frantic about.
Miracle Diet
Well, personally, I actually kind of envy the people
who have something they can get into.
Why didn't I join any clubs?!
What are you saying at this late date?
Oh, well.
Cherry Blossoms
You run at school and run at night as well?
No, I was having a hard time falling asleep,
so I was running because I wanted to feel refreshed.
But after looking at these cherry blossoms,
I'm beginning to think I'll be able to go to sleep.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's something I'm doing because I want to,
and yet I get stressed over it.
I hope you get to go to the Nationals.
Yeah, thanks.
I'll do my best.
Yes!
So, you see, Satchin from Saitama Prefecture,
being dumped is certainly a sad thing,
but you're not the only one in pain when your feelings aren't returned.
That's right. Take Nakku. He's been dumped countless times.
Yeah, that's right.
I've been dumped left and right by girls since I was in school,
and I ended up with the nickname, Emperor of Being Dumped!
Hey, look at what you made me say!
I'm sorry.
This is stupid!
So cheer up, Satchin. We're cheering for you!
Why anyone would send postcards to a show like this, I don't know.
Hang in there!
The pen name on the next postcard is...
Oh! Little Tearful Diet Girl! Oh, I remember you!
This is the girl who's been trying all sorts of dieting methods, right?
Apparently, all she does is diet.
It's not nice to laugh at her, Nakku!
It's a huge problem for girls.
Right, right, I shouldn't be laughing about it.
Let's see, "Nakku, Mitchy, please listen to this."
"This time, I tried the grainless diet."
Wow, the grainless diet!
The grainless diet's the one you tried last month and failed at!
"This is where you don't eat any rice, bread, or noodles."
"Instead, you eat fruits, vegetables, and oily things."
Wait. Don't tell me...
"It's a very revolutionary method of dieting."
Hey! It's a bull's-eye, isn't it?!
"I read about it in a magazine article and immediately tried it."
Whoa! How embarrassing!
"Unlike previous diets, there was no hunger to deal with,"
You send postcards to shows like this!
"So I felt I could keep it up."
Wow, Yomi! This is just embarrassing!
"I thought I'd be extremely lucky if I could lose weight this way,"
"But having run out of ideas in her repertoire,"
Little Tearful Diet Girl, was it?! Oh, so sad!
"My mother made curry and rice for dinner."
Shut up! Shut up!
"Having rice for the first time in three days, it was just delicious."
"It was so delicious, I ended up having seconds!"
Let's see, "The next day, when I weighed myself,"
"I weighed more than I had three days ago!" Of course!
"The enemy of the grainless diet was my mother's menu!"
Don't laugh!
"I intend to keep at it and go on to trying another diet. " That's it.
But you sent it in so people would laugh, right?!
It pisses me off when you're laughing right in front of me!
Eating curry without rice definitely sounds pretty rough.
I'm sorry to hear that, Little Tearful Diet Girl!
Let us know again when you've tried another diet!
Oh, I will!
I'll be rooting for you too!
I'll do my best!
Now, let's move on to the next postcard.
You're an idiot!
You're responding to the radio!
Shut up!
Whoa, Little Tearful Diet Girl!
What's wrong with that?!
There's nothing wrong with it, but it's too funny!
Freedom...
What does that mean?
It's freedom...
Eiko really seemed like she had her stuff together, you know?
She did?
The men that Eiko brought along...
Maybe they thought we were rather childish.
You think so?
I just have this feeling.
It's probably just your imagination.
I think maybe I'll try looking into an arranged marriage.
An arranged marriage?
There's some talk of that sort.
If you want to, why don't you? It's your life.
You're right. It is my life.
So, are you going to do it?
I don't know.
Why is it that spring makes you so sleepy?
That's because you stay up late!
Osaka! Get it together! Really!
Magnificent! A magnificent yawn!
What?
kokoro ni hane wo motte
With wings upon your soul,
tsutaete mune no sasayaki
Convey the whispers of your heart.
ima, kaze ni notte
Now, riding the wind,
kokoro wa hoshi no kanata (hoshi no kanata)
Your soul is beyond the stars (beyond the stars).
negai wa kanarazu kanau
Your wishes will come true, without fail.
ai ni kite sono kagi wa mirai he
Come see me, that key is for the future.
mado ni sotto yobu koe wa
The voice calling softly by the window
koi no yokan soshite
Speaks of love to come and...
mada touku no ai de mo
Even if the love is still far off,
shinjiteru asu wo shinjiteru kimi wo
I have faith in tomorrow, I have faith in you.
Raspberry heaven.
hitori ja naitte yakusoku shita ne heaven
I promised you that you're not alone, remember, heaven?
Raspberry Heaven amai namida
Raspberry heaven... such sweet tears.
rakuen de mata hohoende ne
Smile again in paradise.
Raspberry heaven.
mukae ni kita yasashii yume no heaven
I've come for you, the heaven of gentle dreams.
Raspberry heaven, I'm coming back to you.
rakuen no hana saita hi ni
On the day the flowers in paradise bloom,
kimi to futari...
You and I...
futari de aimashou
Let's meet, just the two of us.
Next
Azumanga
Daioh
After all's said and done,
I guess those guys are already third year students.
It's so fast.
I get the feeling Chiyo-chan's grown quite a bit, too.
Hah! Time flows equally for all people. Ain't it great?
Speaking of which, my students gave me a present for my birthday...
Kurosawa, what did you just say?!
A present...
Presents?! Who cares about birthdays?!
You wanna age that badly?!
I don't really understand, but things will continue next week.